hookuphotshot.com 2017-06-07

# Privacy Policy | Hookup Hotshot

**Effective Date: 1/1/2017**

This privacy notice discloses the privacy practices for hookuphotshot.com. This privacy notice applies solely to information collected by this website, except where stated otherwise. It will notify you of the following:

  * What information we collect
  * With whom it is shared
  * How it can be corrected
  * How it is secured
  * How policy changes will be communicated
  * How to address concerns over misuse of personal data

We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site: usernames, email addresses, and passwords. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. _We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request_ , e.g., to process a payment, to ship an order, or to add you to a mailing list that you sign up for.

Unless you ask us not to, we may contact you via email in the future to tell you about specials, new products or services, or changes to this privacy policy.

You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by filling out [this form](https://hookuphotshot.com/support/):

  * See what data we have about you, if any
  * Change/correct any data we have about you
  * Have us delete any data we have about you
  * Express any concern you have about our use of your data

We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

Wherever we collect information, that information is encrypted and transmitted to us in a secure way. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for “https” at the beginning of the address of the web page.

While we use encryption to protect sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (e.g, billing or customer service) are granted access to personally identifiable information. The servers on which we store personally identifiable information are kept in a secure environment.

Whenever material changes are made to the privacy notice, we will email you about the changes.

If you feel that we are not abiding by this privacy policy, you should contact us immediately by filling out [this form](https://hookuphotshot.com/support/).
